<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>PittCrew News</title>
	<atom:link href="http://pittcrew.net/news/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>http://pittcrew.net/news</link>
	<description>News and events in the life of the Pitt Crew</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sun, 13 Jul 2008 22:39:31 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>http://wordpress.org/?v=3.4.2</generator>
		<item>
		<title>Oh, Canada!</title>
		<link>http://pittcrew.net/news/2007/03/17/oh-canada/</link>
		<comments>http://pittcrew.net/news/2007/03/17/oh-canada/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Sun, 18 Mar 2007 03:15:58 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator>Kenny</dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[General]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://pittcrew.net/news/2007/03/17/oh-canada/</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Tonight was St. Patrick&#8217;s Day at the Gwinnett Gladiators hockey game. The ice was green, and the arena was filled with 10,349 screaming fans. But wait! Who&#8217;s that walking out onto the ice? &#8220;Here&#8217;s Jennifer Pitt to perform Oh, Canada!&#8221; That&#8217;s right, Jennifer was singing solo in front of over 10,000 people at a professional [...]]]></description>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Tonight was St. Patrick&#8217;s Day at the <a href="http://www.gwinnettgladiators.com/">Gwinnett Gladiators</a> hockey game. The ice was green, and the arena was filled with 10,349 screaming fans. But wait! Who&#8217;s that walking out onto the ice?</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;Here&#8217;s Jennifer Pitt to perform <em>Oh, Canada</em>!&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>That&#8217;s right, Jennifer was singing solo in front of over 10,000 people at a professional hockey game. Oh yeah, and the Gladiators also won the game 5&mdash;1.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>http://pittcrew.net/news/2007/03/17/oh-canada/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>David gets braces</title>
		<link>http://pittcrew.net/news/2006/06/06/david-gets-braces/</link>
		<comments>http://pittcrew.net/news/2006/06/06/david-gets-braces/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2006 02:07:16 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator>Kenny</dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[General]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://pittcrew.net/news/?p=11</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[David got his braces installed today. The orthodontist wanted to go ahead and install them on the upper teeth to make more room for the permanent teeth to come in in the front. Braces sure have changed. As you can see, there is very little metal showing besides the wires. And he even got to [...]]]></description>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>David got his braces installed today.  The orthodontist wanted to go ahead and install them on the upper teeth to make more room for the permanent teeth to come in in the front.</p>
<p>Braces sure have changed. As you can see, there is very little metal showing besides the wires. And he even got to pick the colors!</p>
<p><img src="/news/images/david_braces_small.jpg" alt="David's Braces" class="centered" /></p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>http://pittcrew.net/news/2006/06/06/david-gets-braces/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Filling in some holes</title>
		<link>http://pittcrew.net/news/2006/04/09/filling-in-some-holes/</link>
		<comments>http://pittcrew.net/news/2006/04/09/filling-in-some-holes/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Sun, 09 Apr 2006 14:24:52 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator>Kenny</dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Taekwondo]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Vacation]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://pittcrew.net/news/?p=10</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[I think our blog has a leak! Disney Cruises, black belts, All-State Choruses&#8212;I can&#8217;t find any of it! OK, it&#8217;s my own fault for not keeping up, so here&#8217;s a quick recap of some of the things I&#8217;ve missed in the news. We took 2 more Disney Cruises. We took our first Disney Cruise without [...]]]></description>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>I think our blog has a leak! Disney Cruises, black belts, All-State Choruses&mdash;I can&#8217;t find any of it!  OK, it&#8217;s my own fault for not keeping up, so here&#8217;s a quick recap of some of the things I&#8217;ve missed in the news.</p>
<ul>
<li>We took 2 more <a href="http://www.disneycruiseline.com/">Disney Cruises</a>.  We took our first Disney Cruise without the kids back in 2002.  We enjoyed it so much that we had to do it again and bring them along.  We took our first family cruise to the Eastern Caribbean in June 2004.  Then we took an extended-family Christmas Cruise in December 2005 along with our good friends the Hardys and the Mays.</li>
<li>Our good friends and karate instructors, the Stones, opened their own karate school, <a href="http://daculafamilysports.com/frame_home.htm">Dacula Family Sports</a>.  Now we have a great facility to work out in instead of a high school chorus room.</li>
<li>We all now have our black belts in Tae Kwon Do.  Terri and I got ours in December 2004, Jennifer got hers in February 2005, and David got his in July 2005 after AAU Nationals.</li>
<li>We all competed at the 2005 AAU National Championships.  David decided to stay at the brown belt level, and ended up with over 40 competitors in his division.  The rest of us competed at the black belt level for the first time, so we didn&#8217;t fair as well this year.  I did manage to win the silver medal in point sparring, which I was very pleased with given the level of competition.</li>
<li>Jennifer garnered two more perfect scores in her second audition to make the 2006 Georgia Middle School All-State Chorus in Savannah.  After two and a half days of intense rehearsals, she performed 8 songs with the all-girl Treble Chorus.  The concert was absolutely beautiful.  She later performed a solo of one of the songs at church.</li>
</ul>
<p>I&#8217;m sure there are a few other events that I&#8217;ve missed, but at least I feel better that I&#8217;ve filled all the major holes.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>http://pittcrew.net/news/2006/04/09/filling-in-some-holes/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Jennifer makes first cut for All-State Chorus</title>
		<link>http://pittcrew.net/news/2005/10/17/jennifer-makes-first-cut-for-all-state-chorus/</link>
		<comments>http://pittcrew.net/news/2005/10/17/jennifer-makes-first-cut-for-all-state-chorus/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Oct 2005 00:20:03 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator>Kenny</dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[General]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://pittcrew.net/news/?p=9</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Jennifer had her audition for All-State Chorus on Saturday. Each student performed individually for two judges, and the scores of the two judges are averaged. A cutoff score will be set later based on the number of available spots in the Chorus. Jennifer found out her scores today and she received two perfect scores from [...]]]></description>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Jennifer had her audition for All-State Chorus on Saturday. Each student performed individually for two judges, and the scores of the two judges are averaged. A cutoff score will be set later based on the number of available spots in the Chorus. Jennifer found out her scores today and she received two perfect scores from her judges! Even though the final cutoff has not been set, she is guaranteed to make the cut.</p>
<p>There is a second audition in January, but it is mainly to make sure the students are making good progress learning the music for the All-State performance. So it looks like Jennnifer will be singing in Savannah in March. Congratulations, Jennnifer!</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>http://pittcrew.net/news/2005/10/17/jennifer-makes-first-cut-for-all-state-chorus/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>David&#8217;s room is painted!</title>
		<link>http://pittcrew.net/news/2005/09/10/davids-room-is-painted/</link>
		<comments>http://pittcrew.net/news/2005/09/10/davids-room-is-painted/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Sat, 10 Sep 2005 17:18:19 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator>Kenny</dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[General]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://pittcrew.net/news/?p=8</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[We just finished repainting David&#8217;s room. He had outgrown the old decor, and was very excited about helping pick out the new colors. He really wanted to have red and, instead of a traditional comforter, he chose a quilt set with deep burgundy reds and beiges and a sort of cabin-in-the-woods feel. David originally wanted [...]]]></description>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>We just finished repainting David&#8217;s room. He had outgrown the old decor, and was very excited about helping pick out the new colors. He really wanted to have red and, instead of a traditional comforter, he chose a quilt set with deep burgundy reds and beiges and a sort of cabin-in-the-woods feel. David originally wanted the entire room red, but we decide that would be a bit much. When we first decorated his room, we installed beadboard wainscoting around the bottom of the room, so we compromised and painted the wainscoting red and the upper wall and ceiling beige. Now that it&#8217;s all finished, David is very happy with the result.</p>
<p>We had originally planned to finish the room over Labor Day weekend, but we didn&#8217;t quite make it for one main reason: painting beadboard is <em>really</em> hard! It was a painstaking process getting paint into all those grooves, especially when trying to get the deep red to cover the old green. Miraculously, we managed to get by with only two coats or else we might never have gotten finished.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>http://pittcrew.net/news/2005/09/10/davids-room-is-painted/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Jennifer sings a solo</title>
		<link>http://pittcrew.net/news/2005/09/04/jennifer-sings-a-solo/</link>
		<comments>http://pittcrew.net/news/2005/09/04/jennifer-sings-a-solo/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Sun, 04 Sep 2005 22:44:34 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator>Kenny</dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[General]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://pittcrew.net/news/2005/09/04/jennifer-sings-a-solo/</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Jennifer sang her first true solo in church today, just her and the piano accompaniment in front of the whole congregation. Jennifer was very excited when she earned the solo part for the children&#8217;s musical last spring, but unfortunately the musical had to be cancelled and she didn&#8217;t get to sing. The choir director promised [...]]]></description>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Jennifer sang her first true solo in church today, just her and the piano accompaniment in front of the whole congregation. Jennifer was very excited when she earned the solo part for the children&#8217;s musical last spring, but unfortunately the musical had to be cancelled and she didn&#8217;t get to sing. The choir director promised he would find another time when she could do her solo, so today she provided the music during Communion. She did a great job, and received a number of compliments afterwards!</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>http://pittcrew.net/news/2005/09/04/jennifer-sings-a-solo/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Gasoline craziness</title>
		<link>http://pittcrew.net/news/2005/08/31/gasoline-craziness/</link>
		<comments>http://pittcrew.net/news/2005/08/31/gasoline-craziness/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 01 Sep 2005 00:11:13 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator>Kenny</dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[General]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://pittcrew.net/news/?p=6</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[It seems a bit of a panic has broken out here in Atlanta over a possible gasoline shortage. People are lining up at the pumps all over the Atlanta area, and a lot of stations are running dry. Some stations that still have gas available are jacking prices way up as a result. On my [...]]]></description>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>It seems a bit of a panic has broken out here in Atlanta over a possible gasoline shortage. People are lining up at the pumps all over the Atlanta area, and a lot of stations are running dry. Some stations that still have gas available are jacking prices way up as a result. On my way home from work today, I personally saw a station charging $3.49/gal for Regular, but I heard several reports on the radio of prices over $5.00 or even $6.00/gal. It got so bad that the governor had to step in to <a href="http://atlanta.bizjournals.com/atlanta/stories/2005/08/29/daily19.html">prevent further price gouging</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>http://pittcrew.net/news/2005/08/31/gasoline-craziness/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Welcome to the Family News blog</title>
		<link>http://pittcrew.net/news/2005/08/27/welcome-to-the-family-news-blog/</link>
		<comments>http://pittcrew.net/news/2005/08/27/welcome-to-the-family-news-blog/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Sun, 28 Aug 2005 03:21:53 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator>Kenny</dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[General]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://pittcrew.net/news/?p=3</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[The PittCrew Family News is now a blog! I always intended for it to be somewhat blog-like, but adding content to the old Family News page involved too much overhead for quick updates. Now the blog software will manage that overhead for me, and allow me to dash off a quick post from any Web [...]]]></description>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The PittCrew Family News is now a <a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Blog">blog</a>! I always intended for it to be somewhat blog-like, but adding content to the <a href="/familynews.html">old Family News page</a> involved too much overhead for quick updates. Now the blog software will manage that overhead for me, and allow me to dash off a quick post from any Web browser. I&#8217;m hoping that will lead to more frequent updates about all the semi-interesting (at least to us) little tidbits in our lives. We&#8217;ll see how it goes.</p>
<p>Another feature of the new format is that readers can leave their own comments on a post. I&#8217;m asking that you register your name and e-mail address before posting a comment, but don&#8217;t worry because your e-mail address will never be exposed to other readers. Please register and post a comment to let us know how you like the new format.</p>
<p>And finally, for the geekier types like me, there is now an <a href="http://www.pittcrew.net/news/feed/">RSS feed</a> so that you can get updates without constantly checking the site to see if anything has changed.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>http://pittcrew.net/news/2005/08/27/welcome-to-the-family-news-blog/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Brown belt Tae Kwon Do testing</title>
		<link>http://pittcrew.net/news/2003/12/11/brown-belt-tae-kwon-do-testing/</link>
		<comments>http://pittcrew.net/news/2003/12/11/brown-belt-tae-kwon-do-testing/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2003 14:00:33 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator>Kenny</dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Taekwondo]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://pittcrew.net/news/?p=31</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[The entire Pitt Crew has now reached the brown belt level in Tae Kwon Do. Terri and Kenny moved up from red belt to their first stripe brown belt, and Jennifer and David both received their second stripe brown belts. After the third brown belt stripe, the next level will be black belt. (From old [...]]]></description>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The entire Pitt Crew has now reached the brown belt level in Tae Kwon Do.  Terri and Kenny moved up from red belt to their first stripe brown belt, and Jennifer and David both received their second stripe brown belts.  After the third brown belt stripe, the next level will be black belt.</p>
<p><em>(From old Family News page)</em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>http://pittcrew.net/news/2003/12/11/brown-belt-tae-kwon-do-testing/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>David loses his first tooth</title>
		<link>http://pittcrew.net/news/2003/12/04/david-loses-his-first-tooth/</link>
		<comments>http://pittcrew.net/news/2003/12/04/david-loses-his-first-tooth/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2003 14:28:49 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator>Kenny</dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[General]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://pittcrew.net/news/?p=32</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[David is very excited because he finally lost his first tooth! It had been loose for quite a while, but just didn&#8217;t want to let go. The permanent tooth was already starting to come in behind it so he may not have a gap for too long, but the tooth next to it is already [...]]]></description>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>David is very excited because he finally lost his first tooth!  It had been loose for quite a while, but just didn&#8217;t want to let go.  The permanent tooth was already starting to come in behind it so he may not have a gap for too long, but the tooth next to it is already loose also and he may soon be losing another one.</p>
<p><em>(From old Family News page)</em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>http://pittcrew.net/news/2003/12/04/david-loses-his-first-tooth/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
